Hello everyone, this is Haruka Koizumi, aka Oharu!
Today, July 25th, is Hito-chan's birthday!
Happy birthday!
I told Hito-chan that I would make a birthday video for her today, and I'm going to make a video for her.
I think we made a free talk video with Kanamin last time.
And this time
I'm going to make a surprise for Hito-chan.
I'm going to make a surprise for Hito-chan this time.
The name of it is
I'm going to surprise Hito-chan
to think it's a free talk.
in a game of "Shiritori" (word game)
I'm going to make a lot of videos with Hito-chan from now on.
I'm going to make a lot of videos with Hito-chan.
I'm going to make Hito-chan think it's a free talk video like the last video with Kanamin.
Hito-chan's answer to the question, for example, "I said it's something...".
I'm going to make it look like a free talk video like the last one I did with Kanamin.
I'm going to make it look like a free talk video like the last time I did it with Kanamin, but I'm going to make it look like a Shiritori video.
I'm going to make a video of the free talk and see when Hito-chan realizes it.
I've never done this before, so I'll be asking questions and giving answers in this Shiritori video.
I've never done this before, so I don't know how to ask questions and answer in this Shiritori.
I don't know if it will work or not.
I don't know if I'll be able to do it well.
I don't know if it will go well, but I'll try my best.
So, I don't know...
I'm wondering if it's difficult for you to answer a question and then take it to the next question.
I'm thinking that it might be difficult for you to answer one question and take it to the next.
That's why I'm only going to do the opening.
I'm going to ignore the Shiritori rule
and
I'm going to start with the first question and start using the Shiritori rule.
I'll start with the first question.
So, I'd like to see if you guys can make my Shiritori.
I hope you all enjoy the show and please check out Hito-chan's reaction.
Let's go for today! Let's go!
Yes, it's Hito-chan's birthday today!Yes, so today is Hito-chan's birthday birthday!
Happy Birthday!
So, what we are doing this year is a free talk video for everyone.
I'm going to do a free talk video for everyone.
I'm going to ask Hito-chan a lot of questions.
I'm going to be 22 years old.
I'm turning 22, so I'm going to ask Hito-chan, who's turning 22, a lot of questions.
I'm going to ask Hito-chan, who's turning 22, a lot of questions.
Let's go!
So, let's go.
First of all, Hito-chan.
Is there anything you want to do when you turn 22?
What would you like to do when you turn 22?
Ride a helicopter.
I'd like to go to Rumalia.
What's that? I want to go on a balloon ride.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I know, I know. I know.
It's good, right?
It's good.
And, you know what else?
I wanna go for a ride.
I wanna go surfing or something.
I want to do it now.
Right now? I wanna do it right now. I want to do it right now. I want to go home.
But you're probably not good at it, right, Haachan? No, you're right... you're not good at it.
Maybe not, but I have a goal to swim this year, so... I don't know.
I don't know. He's been saying that for a long time.
He's been saying this for a long time.
He wants to swim.
I wonder how much time has passed since then.
I think it's been quite a while.
I guess so.
I haven't been able to go swimming,
A little,A little,
I hope you can make it this year.
I've never been able to swim before.
I'm getting older, so let's give it a shot, even if it's with a sappa!
I'm going to try it on a big paddle board that's like a big surfing board that's stable.
I'll sit on it, or I'll roll it like this, and it'll be fun.
But, to you, Hito-chan...
Okay, next question.
Now that you're 22 years old...
Is there someone you'd like to meet?
Someone you'd like to meet?
No, I don't.
I don't know.
You mean someone you've never met, right? What? You mean you've never met him?
Right, right, right, right.
Someone you've never met and would like to meet.
Someone I'd like to meet.
Like the Totoro next door.
What's this?
Someone you've never met and would like to meet.
I want to meet a thing, or a person, or a thing.
I'd like to meet... I'd like to meet that...
Um...
That one.
I want to meet my favorite character.
Oh no, it's suddenly not coming out
Great, Howl! Yes, Howl! Meet Howl... You know what? Howl! Yes! Howl!
I want to see Howl!
Yes, yes, yes.
I love Howl so much.
I love spring, too. Howl.
I want to meet Howl.
He's so cool.
And Kaneki-kun from Tokyo Doul.
Hmmm...yes.Hmmm, yes.
I knew it. I admire cool people, don't I?
Yes, we do.
We should be cool too.
I agree. Let's do our best.
We have a tour coming up, so we'll do our best,
What question do you think I'll ask next?
What?
What was the first question?
You don't remember.
Well, I'm just trying to keep track of, uh, what I want to do when I'm 22, and who I want to meet.
And who I want to meet.
And what I want to eat.
and what I want to eat.
Nozawana, for example.
I've noticed that.
I noticed.
Did you know? Is it possible that you just now...
What?
I'm just saying a lot of words.
What? What? I'm just saying a lot of words, okay?
Huh? Huh?
Huh?
Hmm?
You were shushing, weren't you? Good, good, good, good, good .... I'm sure I'm missing a lot of conversations, but I thought I was being tricked.
Yes, actually, yes, this time.
I pretended to give Hito-chan a free talk session.
I pretended to give Hito-chan a free talk, but I answered all of her answers with "Shiritori".
What kind of response would you get?
I didn't notice it at all. I didn't notice it at all.
But I thought something was weird.
I thought, why is that start such a start?
I was like, "I definitely want to do it, I definitely want to do it, I definitely want to do it, I definitely want to do it, I definitely want to do it.
And then the name of the country comes up.
Romania.Romania.
I thought, "I never said anything about going to Romania by helicopter.
So, last time I had a normal free talk with Kanamin, I pretended that there was no surprise.
This time, I'm going to give you this surprise.
I see, but I didn't notice it at all.
Oh, really?
I noticed it with the nozawana.
I think they made nozawana the main dish.
Nozawana as something you'd like to try.
You've had it before.
I eat nozawana all the time.
You love it, right, Chiran?
You love it.
I'm not sure if they celebrate it every year, but...
What are they doing to you?
Celebrating...
It's a surprise.
It doesn't seem like it's a blessing.
But, you know, it's very enjoyable every time, and I'm enjoying it.
I've been looking forward to it too.
Thank you.
It's wonderful.
It's wonderful, isn't it?
I'm glad you liked the video. If you thought this video was good, it's wonderful, isn't it?
If you thought this video was good...
And if you think Hito-chan is 22 years old, please click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel.
Please click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel!
If you liked this video, please subscribe!
Hey!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Yeah 〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜
Congratulations 〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜